

PARIA SABET

FRONTEND WEB DEVELOPER

PROFILE

26 years old who is creative and motivated to constantly learn new skills and to grow professionally.

I am confident in giving new and unique ideas which would set me apart from the rest.

My ideal living would be combing technology with art.

CONTACT

Email: pariasabet13@gmail.com

Phone: +989124576392 Github: Pariasabet Codepen: Pariasabet13 LinkedIn: @Pariasabet Instagram: @Pariasabet13

EDUCATION

GUILAN UNIVERSITY - RASHT, IRAN SEP 2012 - DEC 2017

Bachelor of Software Engineering

SKILLS

PROFICIENT

- Frontend development for responsive web pages
- C# programming
- ASP.net MVC, ASP.net core
- CSS & SASS, Responsive UI design
- JavaScript & JQuery
- Bootstrap and Material Design
- Angular and ReactJs frameworks
- PWA implementation
- SQL Databases(SQL server)
- · Visual Studio, Photoshop, Indesign, sketch, Illustrator
- English Language (IELTS 7.5)
- Photography

NOVICE

- Database design
- Python
- VUE.Js

WORK EXPERIENCE

KHARAZMI IT DEVELOPMENT COMPANY - TEHRAN JAN 2019 - PRESENT

- Part of the web developer team
- Implemented CRM & help desk websites & services
- Assessed UI & UX designs for technical feasibility
- Worked on PWA apps using Angular
- BPMS implementations with Processmaker
- programmed windows form applications using entity framework and SQL Server

SKLIPPER- RASHT JUL 2014 - DEC 2017

- Frontend development of responsive web apps
- Designed game elements with illustrator and photoshop